Ruth Clifford Engs papers, 1947-2010 C404
Indiana University Archives
- The Saint Meinrad Archabbey Projects, 1954-2012 (Box 19)
  - Conversations in the Abbey, 1954-2012 (Box 19)
    - Father Archabbot Bonaventure Knabel, OSB, Correspondence, drafts, bio, and transcription, 2004-2006 (Box 19)
    - Brother Jerome Croteau, OSB, Correspondence, drafts, transcription, personal essays, and bio, 1989-2006 (Box 19)
    - Father Simeon Daly, OSB, Transcription, drafts, personal essay, and bio, 2000-2006 (Box 19)
    - Father Simeon Daly, OSB, Correspondence and obituary, 2005-2012 (Box 19)
    - Father Cyprian Davis, OSB, Correspondence, transcription, draft, and bio, 1978-2008 (Box 19)
    - Father Camillus Ellspermann, OSB, Correspondence, transcription Selma essay, news clippings, and obituary, 1965-2007 (Box 19)
    - Father Camillus Ellspermann, OSB Memories, 2001 (Box 19)
    - Father Camillus Ellspermann, OSB Reflections: A Personal History, 2005 (Box 19)
    - Brother Terence Griffin, OSB, Correspondence, transcription, draft, and bio, 2000-2012 (Box 19)
    - Father Theodore Heck, OSB, Transcriptions, draft, obituary, and bio, 2000-2009 (Box 19)
    - Father Columba Kelly, OSB, Transcription, draft, correspondence, printed material, and bio, 1998-2006 (Box 19)
    - Father Eric Lies, OSB, Transcription, draft, bio, obituary, and printed material, 1994-2012 (Box 19)
    - Father Rupert Ostdick, Correspondence, transcription, drafts, and bio, 2000-2007 (Box 19)
    - Gerald Wikite, Correspondence, transcriptions, and printed materials, 2005-2007 (Box 19)
    - Brother Maurus Zoeller, OSB, Correspondence, transcription, and bio, 2000-2007 (Box 19)
    - Abbey Press, Draft, correspondence, and printed material, 1954-2007 (Box 20)
    - Sample of Abbey Press Catalogues, 1963-2006 (Box 20)
    - Daniel Schipp, Correspondence and transcriptions, 2005-2006 (Box 20)
    - John Wilson, Correspondence and transcription, 2005-2006 (Box 20)
    - Drafts, 2005-2007 (Box 20)
    - Correspondence, 2007 (Box 20)
    - Final Draft, 2007 (Box 20)
    - Other correspondence, 2010-2012 (Box 20)